<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>spring2023 on ENMU CS Club</title>
    <link>/tags/spring2023/</link>
    <description>Recent content in spring2023 on ENMU CS Club</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 16:09:22 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/spring2023/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project // BWDM Augmented Reality Sandbox</title>
      <link>/posts/bwdm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 16:09:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/bwdm/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ll be helping the Blackwater Draw Museum set up their augmented reality sandbox. At one point it worked, but now it doesn&amp;rsquo;t.
So, if on campus members wanted to work on it, please let me know and we can set up a date and time to meet up. These events can be livestreamed for our remote members, too!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>March // Vote on the next meeting date and time</title>
      <link>/posts/votenextmeeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 15:58:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/votenextmeeting/</guid>
      <description>Please vote here!
You can take the survey more than once if you have more than one day or time that you&amp;rsquo;d be available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>March 2 // Student Organization Fair</title>
      <link>/posts/studentorgfair/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 15:58:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/studentorgfair/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR: When Where 3/2, 10:00am-2:00pm MT Ballroom in CUB, 2nd floor Further Detail We&amp;rsquo;ll have a table at the upcoming Student Organization Fair in the CUB Ballroom on the second floor on March 2nd. Please let me know if you&amp;rsquo;re interested in helping out with the table!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feb 10 // First Meeting 2023</title>
      <link>/posts/first-meeting-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 12:22:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/first-meeting-2023/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR: When Where Link 2/10, 5:30pm MT Zuni room in CUB, downstairs here (closed) Further Detail Our first meeting this semester will be Friday the 10th at 5:30pm.
Physical location is Zuni in the CUB building, downstairs. I&amp;rsquo;d like to find a room with a mic that can pick up in person members better, as that was a recurring issue last semester.
The agenda for the first meeting will be discussing the organization and our plans for this semester, so please feel free to brainstorm and speak up should you have a good idea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intro</title>
      <link>/posts/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 12:10:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/intro/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR: This site is for:
Wider collaboration from outside the club Publicly viewable information for non-members to view Record of past projects, events, and meetings Ongoing project for members to participate directly with Further Detail I&amp;rsquo;d like this website to be a platform and archive for club activities and a connection with the general public. I&amp;rsquo;d also like this to be a website that all members can contribute to, so it&amp;rsquo;s on github.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
